# Hani Abdelbasset Elshafei

## **GIS EXPERT** GEO-SPATIAL APPS DEVELOPER **SPATIAL DATA SCIENTIST**

#### CONTACT

Main Address Elmansoura, Egypt Secondary Address Hadayk Elahram , Cairo, Egypt

Phone 01270636492

E-mail hanyelshafey@outlook.com

facebook.com/elshafeysurvey

**Githup**:https://github.com/hanyelshafey

### WORK EXPERIENCE

July 2011 - August 2008 alarabya Urban Development

August 2009 - December 2017

abnia consulting Engineers fahd alhomrany consulting Engineers

January 2017 - Present

#### **East Survey**

The owner of East Survey & team Leader and spatial expert

- \* Supporting companies in managing spatial teams (surveying teams - data collection teams - technical office teams to processing and store surveying data)
- \* Supporting companies in creating surveying sections and producing maps
- \* I can link GIS with programming using Python to facilitate frequent and many tasks
- \* Git and Githup
- \* Web APIs
- \* Rest Framework
- \* Geo-database Design
- \* Geoprocessing and Model Builder. Python experience.
- \* Python language programmer
- \* Developing Geo-spatial apps with Python and Arcpy including design spatial Gui
- \*Using ArcGIS for Desktop and Geo database Administration\Configuration
- \*(Using and administrating ArcGIS Enterprise products (Server, Portal...etc.)
- \* Knowledge of web client development technologies like: HTML5, CSS 3.0, Bootstrap
- \* Pandas & Geopandas & Numpy

#### PROFILE

I established East Survey Company for Surveying Services and Geographic Information Systems, and I delegated its management to my brother. I am now full-time to work on research projects between

Linkedin:linkedin.com/in/hany-elshafey-51ab802b/ programming and geographic information systems and I love to cooperate in any projects in geographic information systems.

#### EDUCATION

#### 2020 - Now

#### **University of MANSOURA**

I currently study Master of Spatial Data Science in Geography and Gis Department

#### **University of MANSOURA**

I studied geographic systems , survey and maps with agood high rating the third 2007 My graduation project was a digital cartography project with honors

#### **On-line courses**

#### **University of California, Davis**

- 1-Fundamentals of GIS
- 2-GIS Data Formats, Design and Quality
- 3-Geospatial and Environmental Analysis
- 4-Imagery, Automation, and Applications
- 5-Geospatial Analysis Project

#### YONSEI UNIVERSITY

1-Spatial Data Science and Applications

#### **Udemy**

- 1-Python Programming
- 2-ArcPy for Python Developers using ArcGIS Pro
- 3-arc pro
- 4-Qgis(pyggis)
- 5 Geodjango

#### Esri

- 1-Python Programming
- 2-ArcGIS API for Python Fundamentals
- 3- Topography
- 4-ArcGIS Enterprise)

#### REFERENCES

mahmoud aboelaa •abniaconsulting Engineers **GIS DEP** 

00966562292893